The Future Just Got Darker
Nemesis 2: Nebula is a science fiction, action,
thriller film directed by Albert Pyun.
It has been 73 years since Alex failed and the Humans lost the Cyborg Wars.
Since then, the Humans have been enslaved.
Scientists have developed a new DNA strain, which could signal the end
of the Cyborgs, and they inject it into a volunteer.
When the Cyborgs learn of the woman and the baby they list both for termination.
Alex, played by Sue Price.
Nebula, played by Chad Stahelski.
Emily, played by Tina Cote.
Po / Juna, played by Earl White.
Zumi / Rebel #2, played by Jahi J.J. Zuri.
Zana, played by Karen Studer.
Nemesis 2: Nebula is a 1995 science fiction film directed by Albert Pyun.
The sequel to Nemesis (1992), it stars Sue Price,
Tina Coté, Earl White, Jahi J.J.
Zuri, and Chad Stahelski.
Nemesis 2 was shot in Globe, Arizona.
It was followed by Nemesis 3: Prey Harder and Nemesis
4: Death Angel, both released in 1996.
Is the second installment in the Nemesis film series.
A compilation version exists which combined the four Nemesis films into one 100-minute feature
that Scanbox was going to release before the company went bankrupt in 2000.
This version was released only in Eastern Europe in 2003, primarily in Poland.
The film explores themes of cyborg, post-apocalyptic future, sequel, cyberpunk.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.